welcome to sri was free consultant
youtube channel
friends today i am showing
were taken is a numbered agent new agent
or from other company to
ics element advisor
portable t
or freshers
what they can firstly icc number
agency
to start their career
so
when you
give
minimum documents and if you are getting
a
id generated like im code
so how you can able to login how you can
able to get the password if your forget
password also
you can generate this subway
just go for forgot password
and enter your imid
and your pan number and submit it
so you will this id will be
registered mail id you will get
password from there you can reset the
password and you can log in
you can start your
business
thank you friends
for watching srivashvik consultants
subscribe my channel
press bell icon button
to get latest video notifications
take care bye see you